videowood.tv 2018-12-28

# VideoWood.tv - Host and Watch Videos Online

Your privacy is important to Videowood. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that Videowood collects, and the ways in which Videowood uses that personal information. 

## Personal information collection

Videowood may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

  * information about your use of this website (including uploaded videos);
  * information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the website (including Facebook® account ID and e-mail address);
  * any other information that you send to Videowood.

## Using personal information

Videowood may use your personal information to:

  * administer this website;
  * personalize the website for you;
  * enable your access to and use of the website services;
  * publish information about you on the website;
  * send to you products that you purchase;
  * supply to you services that you purchase;
  * send to you statements and invoices;
  * collect payments from you;
  * send you marketing communications.

Your private information will be also shared when the following conditions are met:

  * User uploads prohibited content (See Terms and Conditions for Definition);
  * User exploits VideoWood for illegitimate purposes;
  * User used stolen payment credentials

Any of the following nullify our privacy obligations towards the user, which can result in sharing of your private information with a 3rd party.

Videowood discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, Videowood may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

## Securing your data

Videowood will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

Videowood will store all the personal information you provide [on its secure servers].

[Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website will be protected by encryption technology.]

## Cross-border data transfers

Information that Videowood collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which Videowood operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

[In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world.]

You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

## Updating this statement

Videowood may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

## Contact Videowood

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or Videowood's treatment of your personal information, please contact us.
